<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/Wal/Desktop/Darkest Dungeon/My Mods/Oks_TheHell/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>The Hell</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>trinkets</Tags>
		<Tags>gameplay</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[h1]The Hell[/h1]

The Hell is like a new DLC that bring you more endgame content. New potions, new trinkets, farmable boss with specifics loot and new boss difficulty. See in Features for more details.

The vision of the mod is to add more content to the original game and have maximum compatibilities with other mods so that you can customize your game as you like it.
	
[h1]Works with build:[/h1] 23941

[h1]Features:[/h1]

[b]V1:[/b] [i][b]Welcome to the Nightmare[/b][/i]

[b]Supply:[/b] Add 6 new potions to buy at the shopkeeper and 1 Coin.
	* Vigorous Concoction : 15% MAX HP + 5% PROT + 20% Healing Skills. Cost 450 gold.
	* Concentrated Luck : 15% Stun chance + 15% Blight chance  + 15% Bleed chance + 15% Move chance. Cost 350 gold.
	* Offensive Elixir : 15% All Damage + Crit 3%. Cost 450 gold.
	* Evasive Solution : 8 DODGE + 2 SPD. Cost 350 gold.
	* Precisive Solution : 8 ACC + 2 SPD. Cost 350 gold.
	* Resistance Tonic : 20% Bleed resist + 20% Blight resist + 20% Stun resist + 20% Disease resist + 20% Move resist. Cost 450 gold.
	* Bronze Coin to summon Champion Boss, cost 2000 gold. (v1.06)
	
[b]Shopkeeper:[/b]
	* Increased shopkeeper inventory size to 22.
	* Potions stack to 4 for short dungeon.
	* Potions stack to 6 for medium dungeon.
	* Potions stack to 8 for long dungeon.
	* Potions stack to 10 for epic dungeon.

[b]Trinket:[/b] Add 48 new trinkets &amp; 1 new &quot;rarities&quot;. [i]Description on youtube[/i]
	* 12 &quot;collector&quot; trinkets.
	* 22 &quot;tarot&quot; trinkets.
	* 4 &quot;ancestral shambler&quot; trinkets.
	* 5 &quot;very rare&quot; trinkets.
	* 3 &quot;rare&quot; trinkets
	* 2 &quot;uncommon&quot; trinkets.
	* Remove kickstarter Trinkets for compatibility issue with T.O.P.
	* &quot;Tarot&quot; can now be looted more than once. (v1.01)
	* &quot;Tarot&quot; have 50% chance to loot on Champion Boss (v1.05)
	
[b]Curio:[/b] (v1.03)
 - Ruins:
	* Suit of Armor + Bronze Coin = Prophet
	* Locked Sarcophagus + Bronze Coin = Necromancer
 - Warrens:
	* Bone Altar + Bronze Coin = Formless Flesh
	* Sacrificial Stone + Bronze Coin = Swine Prince
 - Weald:
	* Pristine Fountain + Bronze Coin = Hag
	* Traveler&apos;s Tent + Bronze Coin = Brigand Pounder
 - Cove:
	* Ship&apos;s Figurehead + Bronze Coin = Drowned Crew
	* Fish Idol + Bronze Coin = Siren

[b]Boss:[/b]
	* Champion Boss can now loot 22 new &quot;tarot&quot; trinkets.
	* The Shambler can now loot 4 new &quot;ancestral shambler&quot; trinkets.
	* The Collector can now loot 12 new &quot;collector&quot; trinkets.
	
[b]V2:[/b] [i][b]There will be no Mercy[/b][/i]

[b]Trinket:[/b] Add 30 new trinkets &amp; 2 new &quot;rarities&quot;. [i]Description on youtube[/i]
	* 5 &quot;bones&quot; trinkets. Can only be looted once.
	* 25 &quot;seasonal&quot; trinkets. Can only be looted once.
	* &quot;Tarot&quot; have 100% chance to loot on Darkest Dungeon Boss (v2.02)

[b]Monster:[/b]
	* Bone Bearer can now loot (50% chance) the new &quot;bones&quot; trinkets.
	
[b]Hero:[/b]
	* Antiquarian can now loot the new &quot;seasonal&quot; trinkets.
	
[b]Supply:[/b]
	* Added the Silver Coin (Cost 5000 gold) to summon Darkest Dungeon Bosses.

[b]Boss:[/b]
	* Darkest Dungeon Boss have 100% chance to loot the &quot;tarot&quot; trinkets.

[b]Curio:[/b]
	* Added one new curio, The Hell&apos;s Altar. Can be found in rooms in all dungeons.
	* Hell&apos;s Altar + Bronze Coin = Random Champion Boss.
	* Hell&apos;s Altar + Silver Coin = Random Darkest Dungeon Boss.
	* Hell&apos;s Altar + Holy Water = 15% Virtue Buff for the party. (v2.02)
		
[h1]Changelog:[/h1]	

v1.0:
See in Features: [i][b]Welcome to the Nightmare[/b][/i]

v1.01: 
Removed Stacking inventory. Can now be downloaded seperatly in [url=http://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=950430226]Oks Mod Collection[/url]. So that you can customize your game as you like it.
Removed Level restriction for dongeons. Can now be downloaded seperatly in [url=http://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=950430226]Oks Mod Collection[/url]. So that you can customize your game as you like it.
Resistance Tonic cost now 350, was previously 750.
Offensive Elixir cost now 350, was previously 250.
Tarot Cards can now be looted more than once.

v1.02:
Many change was made to the Potions, have in mind that they are for endgame content, feedback are welcome.
Potions price increased from 100 Gold. 
New stats added and some stats increased.
Fight Last to 3, previously 4. 
See in Features: [i][b]Welcome to the Nightmare[/b][/i]

v1.03:
Repeatable quest was broken and not worked like we wanted, is now removed.
All Champion boss can now be summoned like the Shambler with a torch on curio in their appropriate dungeons.
See in Features: [i][b]Welcome to the Nightmare[/b][/i] and Screenshot.

v1.04:
Fixed Siren not spawning.
Boss can be summoned in all difficulties and wont crash the game anymore.
Fixed Swordsman&apos;s Crest buff text.

v1.05: 
Reduced Tarot Trinket loot chance to 50%.

v1.06:
Increased shopkeeper size to 20 in preparation for V2.
Added bronze coin (Cost 2000 gold) to the shopkeeper to summon Champion Boss instead of torch.
Fixed a bug with The Prophet.

v2.0:
See in Features: [i][b]There will be no Mercy[/b][/i]

v2.01: 
Increased spawning rates of Hell&apos;s Altar.

v2.02:
We are not satisfied with the Master Boss right now, there a now removed and will come back later in V3 and will be summoned with Gold Coin. As you can seen on this screen we have better plans for it. http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=963571297
Bronze Coin on Hell&apos;s Altar will now summon a random Champion Boss, you have now many ways to farm them.
Silver Coin on Hell&apos;s Altar will now summon a random Darkest Dungeon Boss, they have 100% chance to loot the Tarot Trinkets.
New interaction: Holy Water + Hell&apos;s Altar = 15% Virtue buff for the party.
Fixed the spawning bug for one champion boss (Brigand Vvulf).
Fixed the spawning bug for one Darkest Dungeon boss (Cyst).

v2.03:
Fixed a bug with test files.

v2.04:
Fixed a bug with Virtue Buff on Hell&apos;s Altar Curio.

v2.05:
Improve compatibilty and reorganize trinket rarities.
Increased shopkeeper size to 22 in preparation for The Hell - Crimson Court.
Fixed a bug with Shambler Altar appearing too many times in Warrens and Weald.
Fixed some trinkets price.

v2.06:
The Heart of Darkness (summonable with silver coin) wont kill 2 heroes anymore each time you face him.

v2.07:
Update for compatibility with The Hell - Crimson Court

v2.08:
Seasonal Trinkets can now only be looted once.

v2.09: 
Update/Fix for The Color of Madness DLC.
 

[h1]Compatibility with my mods:[/h1]

3 Trinkets: YES
Remove Dungeons Level Restriction: YES 
Inventory Stack: YES
Faster Combat: YES
Faster Walking: YES
Better Trinkets: NO 

[h1]Compatibility with other mods:[/h1]

Skins: YES
Classes: YES. Classes with trinkets only if they are made like the classes from Exaelus with the trinkets in separated file. 
Trinkets: YES. Trinkets should be in separated files like we did. (T.O.P. is compatible)
Trinkets Rarities: YES
Inventory: YES
Provision: YES but not for buyable provision. New provision like this added by the Enigma class from Exaelus is fine.
Loot Table: YES only for new loot table in separated files.
Quest: YES
Dungeon: NO, Summoned monster like we did cant be in separeted files so we need to use the original dungeons mash files.
Curio: NO
Boss: YES 
Monster: YES only if they are in separeted dungeons mash files.

If you need more space at the shopekeeper, download https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=971739695&amp;searchtext=exaelus from Exaelus, it was made to be full compatible with The Hell.

[h1]Credits:[/h1]

Oks
Epsy
Maester Silvio - Thanks for his awesome work on Pitch Black Dungeon and for leting me use trinkets (V1 and V2 artwork and stats) and potions/coins (V1 and V2 artwork) from his mod. Link to PBD: https://steamcommunity.com/app/262060/discussions/4/618453594742937266/
RedDyeNo5 - Artwork
Monsoontide - Artwork
Tacocat - Artwork

[h1]Support:[/h1]

If you&apos;d like to donate because of my additional work on this or my other mods, go [url=https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_donations&amp;business=R4BABWAKJZ9AA&amp;lc=FR&amp;item_name=Oks&amp;currency_code</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>953578540</PublishedFileId>
</project>

