<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/Sean/Desktop/Darkest Dungeon Mods/Lord&apos;s Blade/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Lord&apos;s Blade</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>2</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Dark Souls</Tags>
		<Tags>Tactical</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>CoM Compatible! Synergy with Abysswalker! https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1225113804
	
	[h1]Class Introduction:[/h1]

Lord&apos;s Blade is based upon Lord&apos;s Blade Ciaran from Dark Souls. She is an assassin class with lots of set-up burst, attacking with unique blades which bleed or blight enemies. Outside of burst damage, she excels at debuffing enemies while applying bleeds and blights. Her trinkets grant further utility, allowing her to specialize from mission-to-mission.

She works well with people who cast bleed or blight abilities. This allows her to activate her full damage sooner. She can also mark or debuff an enemy, guiding ally attacks.

Because of their relationship, Abysswalker and Lord&apos;s Blade have a few (strong) bonuses for each other at the campfire and in combat.  More synergy will develop between these mods in the future.

[h1]Art Credit:[/h1]

AceroSteel drew the character art, and frankly he rocked it. Praise him as you would the Sun!

[h1]Combat Skills:[/h1]

[b]Mutilate:[/b]

- O O O  v  X X - -

Lord&apos;s Blade moves forward 1, attacking the enemy with both enchanted blades. It gains immense damage if an enemy is blighted and/or bled. If bled, great additional damage and accuracy %. If blighted, great additional damage and crit%.

[b]Backstab:[/b]

O O O -  v   X X X -

Lord&apos;s Blade moves forward 2, backstabbing the enemy. Extra damage on marked targets and armor pen on blighted targets.

[b]Golden Strike:[/b]

O O O O  v X X X X 

Lord&apos;s Blade hurls a Golden Tracer at an enemy. Upon successful hit, it bleeds the enemy, marking the enemy for 6 turns, and lowering its defense. Bleed lasts for longer durations with each level. Reduces bleed resistance.

[b]Fast Roll:[/b]

- - O O

Lord&apos;s Blade dodges backwards 2 spaces, gaining 1 turn of stealth and a few turns of +Dodge.

[b]Thrown Tracer:[/b]

O O - -  v - X X X

Lord&apos;s Blade throws her Golden Tracer at an enemy, and gains a large damage bonus upon marked targets. Also gains armor pen on blighted targets.

[b]Silver Strike: [/b]

- - O O  v  X X X X

Lord&apos;s Blade throws a Silver Tracer at an enemy. Upon successful hit, it applies crippling poison which blights and reduces enemy speed. Blight lasts for longer durations with each level. Reduces blight resistance.

[b]Estus Brew:[/b]

O O O O 

Lord&apos;s Blade heals herself, cures herself, and gains another turn. Free action. 1 time per combat. You can use this for easy set-up, or to unload 2 straight turns of set-up damage. Be warned: it severely reduces her defensive abilities, and marks her.


[h1]Camp Skills:[/h1]

In addition to the normal camp skills, Lord Blade has...

[b]Companionship:[/b] Lord&apos;s Blade reminisces about her beloved companion. If she targets an Abysswalker, grants buffs specific to that class.
[b]Lurker:[/b] Lord&apos;s Blade imbues herself in the shadows, foiling any ambush plot, ignoring stealthed enemies, and reducing chances of being surprised.
[b]Lloyd&apos;s Sagely Wisdom:[/b] Lord&apos;s Blade consults the wise words of Allfather Lloyd, giving random buffs to team-mates.
[b]Envenom:[/b] Lord&apos;s Blade buffs the party&apos;s chance to bleed and blight.

[h1]Trinkets:[/h1]
 
[b]Lloyd&apos;s Talisman:[/b] Reduce enemy healing received to 0 on attacks. 10% stress damage taken. Increases ranged damage. Increases crit chance received on enemy target.
[b]Hornet Ring:[/b] 25% crit and 30% damage against marked targets. 10% stress damage taken.
[b]Corrosive Brew:[/b] Gains 40% debuff chance against poisoned targets. If enemy&apos;s poisoned, 100% chance to debuff their protection by 30% on offensive attack. 10% stress damage taken.
[b]Barbed Wire:[/b] Gains 40% debuff chance against bleeding targets. If enemy&apos;s bleeding, 100% chance to reduce dodge by 25. 10% stress damage taken.
[b]Ambush Ring:[/b] Gains bonus damage when attacking from stealth. 10% stress damage taken.

[h1] Media: [/h1]

Slayer1557 made a great introduction &amp; review of Lord&apos;s Blade! Link here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FikjwPEcw9c
[h1]Final Thoughts:[/h1]

I shot for ~3 different build types here. Mutilate focus, backstab focus, and ranged dagger focus. I&apos;m sure people will mix and match abilities while adding other classes to the party, but I&apos;m quite happy with the class&apos; own potential to set itself up.

[h1]A Friendly Request:[/h1]

I like feedback. Please keep it to the forums, though-- comments for my mod are intended to be short messages, or urgent ones about bugs. 

[h1]Future plans:[/h1]

-Updates for ability icon art and weapon/armor art will come soon.
-CC Trinkets &amp; CoM Trinkets are drafted. CC Trinkets will come soon. CoM Trinkets will come with a Darkest Souls Trinket mod.
-Sir Alonne will be my masterpiece. He&apos;s coming soon.</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1433161277</PublishedFileId>
</project>

